<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
contains non-kitten items description for robotfindskitten
see http://www.crummy.com/software/robotfindskitten/
-->
<root>
<item>&quot;I pity the fool who mistakes me for kitten!&quot;, sez Mr. T.</item>
<item>That&apos;s just an old tin can.</item>
<item>It&apos;s an altar to the horse god.</item>
<item>A box of dancing mechanical pencils. They dance! They sing!</item>
<item>It&apos;s an old Duke Ellington record.</item>
<item>A box of fumigation pellets.</item>
<item>A digital clock. It&apos;s stuck at 2:17 PM.</item>
<item>That&apos;s just a charred human corpse.</item>
<item>I don&apos;t know what that is, but it&apos;s not kitten.</item>
<item>An empty shopping bag. Paper or plastic?</item>
<item>Could it be... a big ugly bowling trophy?</item>
<item>A coat hanger hovers in thin air. Odd.</item>
<item>Not kitten, just a packet of Kool-Aid(tm).</item>
<item>A freshly-baked pumpkin pie.</item>
<item>A lone, forgotten comma, sits here, sobbing.</item>
<item>ONE HUNDRED THOUSAND CARPET FIBERS!!!!!</item>
<item>It&apos;s Richard Nixon&apos;s nose!</item>
<item>It&apos;s Lucy Ricardo. &quot;Aaaah, Ricky!&quot;, she says.</item>
<item>You stumble upon Bill Gates&apos; stand-up act.</item>
<item>Just an autographed copy of the Kama Sutra.</item>
<item>It&apos;s the Will Rogers Highway. Who was Will Rogers, anyway?</item>
<item>It&apos;s another robot, more advanced in design than you but strangely immobile.</item>
<item>Leonard Richardson is here, asking people to lick him.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a stupid mask, fashioned after a beagle.</item>
<item>Your State Farm Insurance(tm) representative!</item>
<item>It&apos;s the local draft board.</item>
<item>Seven 1/4&quot; screws and a piece of plastic.</item>
<item>An 80286 machine.</item>
<item>One of those stupid &quot;Homes of the Stars&quot; maps.</item>
<item>A signpost saying &quot;TO KITTEN&quot;. It points in no particular direction.</item>
<item>A hammock stretched between a tree and a volleyball pole.</item>
<item>A Texas Instruments of Destruction calculator.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a dark, amphorous blob of matter.</item>
<item>Just a pincushion.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a mighty zombie talking about some love and prosperity.</item>
<item>&quot;Dear robot, you may have already won our 10 MILLION DOLLAR prize...&quot;</item>
<item>It&apos;s just an object.</item>
<item>A mere collection of pixels.</item>
<item>A badly dented high-hat cymbal lies on its side here.</item>
<item>A marijuana brownie.</item>
<item>A plush Chewbacca.</item>
<item>Daily hunger conditioner from Australasia</item>
<item>Just some stuff.</item>
<item>Why are you touching this when you should be finding kitten?</item>
<item>A glorious fan of peacock feathers.</item>
<item>It&apos;s some compromising photos of Babar the Elephant.</item>
<item>A copy of the Weekly World News. Watch out for the chambered nautilus!</item>
<item>It&apos;s the proverbial wet blanket.</item>
<item>A &quot;Get Out of Jail Free&quot; card.</item>
<item>An incredibly expensive &quot;Mad About You&quot; collector plate.</item>
<item>Paul Moyer&apos;s necktie.</item>
<item>A haircut and a real job. Now you know where to get one!</item>
<item>An automated robot-hater. It frowns disapprovingly at you.</item>
<item>An automated robot-liker. It smiles at you.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a black hole. Don&apos;t fall in!</item>
<item>Just a big brick wall.</item>
<item>You found kitten! No, just kidding.</item>
<item>Heart of Darkness brand pistachio nuts.</item>
<item>A smoking branding iron shaped like a 24-pin connector.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a Java applet.</item>
<item>An abandoned used-car lot.</item>
<item>A shameless plug for Crummy: http://www.crummy.com/</item>
<item>A shameless plug for the UCLA Linux Users Group: http://linux.ucla.edu/</item>
<item>A can of Spam Lite.</item>
<item>This is another fine mess you&apos;ve gotten us into, Stanley.</item>
<item>It&apos;s scenery for &quot;Waiting for Godot&quot;.</item>
<item>This grain elevator towers high above you.</item>
<item>A Mentos wrapper.</item>
<item>It&apos;s the constellation Pisces.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a fly on the wall. Hi, fly!</item>
<item>This kind of looks like kitten, but it&apos;s not.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a banana! Oh, joy!</item>
<item>A helicopter has crashed here.</item>
<item>Carlos Tarango stands here, doing his best impression of Pat Smear.</item>
<item>A patch of mushrooms grows here.</item>
<item>A patch of grape jelly grows here.</item>
<item>A spindle, and a grindle, and a bucka-wacka-woom!</item>
<item>A geyser sprays water high into the air.</item>
<item>A toenail? What good is a toenail?</item>
<item>You&apos;ve found the fish! Not that it does you much good in this game.</item>
<item>A Buttertonsils bar.</item>
<item>One of the few remaining discoes.</item>
<item>Ah, the uniform of a Revolutionary-era minuteman.</item>
<item>A punch bowl, filled with punch and lemon slices.</item>
<item>It&apos;s nothing but a G-thang, baby.</item>
<item>IT&apos;S ALIVE! AH HA HA HA HA!</item>
<item>This was no boating accident!</item>
<item>Wait! This isn&apos;t the poker chip! You&apos;ve been tricked! DAMN YOU, MENDEZ!</item>
<item>A livery stable! Get your livery!</item>
<item>It&apos;s a perpetual immobility machine.</item>
<item>&quot;On this spot in 1962, Henry Winkler was sick.&quot;</item>
<item>There&apos;s nothing here; it&apos;s just an optical illusion.</item>
<item>The World&apos;s Biggest Motzah Ball!</item>
<item>A tribe of cannibals lives here. They eat Malt-O-Meal for breakfast, you know.</item>
<item>This appears to be a rather large stack of trashy romance novels.</item>
<item>Look out! Exclamation points!</item>
<item>A herd of wild coffee mugs slumbers here.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a limbo bar! How low can you go?</item>
<item>It&apos;s the horizon. Now THAT&apos;S weird.</item>
<item>A vase full of artificial flowers is stuck to the floor here.</item>
<item>A large snake bars your way.</item>
<item>A pair of saloon-style doors swing slowly back and forth here.</item>
<item>It&apos;s an ordinary bust of Beethoven... but why is it painted green?</item>
<item>It&apos;s TV&apos;s lovable wisecracking Crow! &quot;Bite me!&quot;, he says.</item>
<item>Hey, look, it&apos;s war. What is it good for? Absolutely nothing. Say it again.</item>
<item>It&apos;s the amazing self-referential thing that&apos;s not kitten.</item>
<item>A flamboyant feather boa. Now you can dress up like Carol Channing!</item>
<item>&quot;Sure hope we get some rain soon,&quot; says Farmer Joe.</item>
<item>&quot;How in heck can I wash my neck if it ain&apos;t gonna rain no more?&quot; asks Farmer Al.</item>
<item>&quot;Topsoil&apos;s all gone, ma,&quot; weeps Lil&apos; Greg.</item>
<item>This is a large brown bear. Oddly enough, it&apos;s currently peeing in the woods.</item>
<item>A team of arctic explorers is camped here.</item>
<item>This object here appears to be Louis Farrakhan&apos;s bow tie.</item>
<item>This is the world-famous Chain of Jockstraps.</item>
<item>A trash compactor, compacting away.</item>
<item>This toaster strudel is riddled with bullet holes!</item>
<item>It&apos;s a hologram of a crashed helicopter.</item>
<item>This is a television. On screen you see a robot strangely similar to yourself.</item>
<item>This balogna has a first name, it&apos;s R-A-N-C-I-D.</item>
<item>A salmon hatchery? Look again. It&apos;s merely a single salmon.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a rim shot. Ba-da-boom!</item>
<item>It&apos;s creepy and it&apos;s kooky, mysterious and spooky. It&apos;s also somewhat ooky.</item>
<item>This is an anagram.</item>
<item>This object is like an analogy.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a symbol. You see in it a model for all symbols everywhere.</item>
<item>The object pushes back at you.</item>
<item>A traffic signal. It appears to have been recently vandalized.</item>
<item>&quot;There is no kitten!&quot; cackles the old crone. You are shocked by her blasphemy.</item>
<item>This is a Lagrange point. Don&apos;t come too close now.</item>
<item>The dirty old tramp bemoans the loss of his harmonica.</item>
<item>Look, it&apos;s Fanny the Irishman!</item>
<item>What in blazes is this?</item>
<item>It&apos;s the instruction manual for a previous version of this game.</item>
<item>A brain cell. Oddly enough, it seems to be functioning.</item>
<item>Tea and/or crumpets.</item>
<item>This jukebox has nothing but Cliff Richards albums in it.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a Quaker Oatmeal tube, converted into a drum.</item>
<item>This is a remote control. Being a robot, you keep a wide berth.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a roll of industrial-strength copper wire.</item>
<item>Oh boy! Grub! Er, grubs.</item>
<item>A puddle of mud, where the mudskippers play.</item>
<item>Plenty of nothing.</item>
<item>Look at that, it&apos;s the Crudmobile.</item>
<item>Just Walter Mattheau and Jack Lemmon.</item>
<item>Two crepes, two crepes in a box.</item>
<item>An autographed copy of &quot;Primary Colors&quot;, by Anonymous.</item>
<item>Another rabbit? That&apos;s three today!</item>
<item>It&apos;s a segmentation fault. Core dumped, by the way.</item>
<item>A historical marker showing the actual location of /dev/null.</item>
<item>Thar&apos;s Mobius Dick, the convoluted whale. Arrr!</item>
<item>It&apos;s a charcoal briquette, smoking away.</item>
<item>A pizza, melting in the sun.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a &quot;HOME ALONE 2: Lost in New York&quot; novelty cup.</item>
<item>A stack of 7 inch floppies wobbles precariously.</item>
<item>It&apos;s nothing but a corrupted floppy. Coaster anyone?</item>
<item>A section of glowing phosphor cells sings a song of radiation to you.</item>
<item>This TRS-80 III is eerily silent.</item>
<item>A toilet bowl occupies this space.</item>
<item>This peg-leg is stuck in a knothole!</item>
<item>It&apos;s a solitary vacuum tube.</item>
<item>This corroded robot is clutching a mitten.</item>
<item>&quot;Hi, I&apos;m Anson Williams, TV&apos;s &apos;Potsy&apos;.&quot;</item>
<item>This subwoofer was blown out in 1974.</item>
<item>Three half-pennies and a wooden nickel.</item>
<item>It&apos;s the missing chapter to &quot;A Clockwork Orange&quot;.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a burrito stand flyer. &quot;Taqueria El Ranchito&quot;.</item>
<item>This smiling family is happy because they eat LARD.</item>
<item>Roger Avery, persona un famoso de los Estados Unidos.</item>
<item>Ne&apos;er but a potted plant.</item>
<item>A parrot, kipping on its back.</item>
<item>A forgotten telephone switchboard.</item>
<item>A forgotten telephone switchboard operator.</item>
<item>It&apos;s an automated robot-disdainer. It pretends you&apos;re not there.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a portable hole. A sign reads: &quot;Closed for the winter&quot;.</item>
<item>Just a moldy loaf of bread.</item>
<item>A little glass tub of Carmex. ($.89) Too bad you have no lips.</item>
<item>A Swiss-Army knife. All of its appendages are out. (toothpick lost)</item>
<item>It&apos;s a zen simulation, trapped within an ASCII character.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a copy of &quot;The Rubaiyat of Spike Schudy&quot;.</item>
<item>It&apos;s &quot;War and Peace&quot; (unabridged, very small print).</item>
<item>A willing, ripe tomato bemoans your inability to digest fruit.</item>
<item>A robot comedian. You feel amused.</item>
<item>It&apos;s KITT, the talking car.</item>
<item>Here&apos;s Pete Peterson. His batteries seem to have long gone dead.</item>
<item>&quot;Blup, blup, blup&quot;, says the mud pot.</item>
<item>More grist for the mill.</item>
<item>Grind &apos;em up, spit &apos;em out, they&apos;re twigs.</item>
<item>The boom box cranks out an old Ethel Merman tune.</item>
<item>It&apos;s &quot;Finding kitten&quot;, published by O&apos;Reilly and Associates.</item>
<item>Pumpkin pie spice.</item>
<item>It&apos;s the Bass-Matic &apos;76! Mmm, that&apos;s good bass!</item>
<item>&quot;Lend us a fiver &apos;til Thursday&quot;, pleas Andy Capp.</item>
<item>It&apos;s a tape of &apos;70s rock. All original hits! All original artists!</item>
<item>You&apos;ve found the fabled America Online disk graveyard!</item>
<item>Empty jewelboxes litter the landscape.</item>
<item>It&apos;s the astounding meta-object.</item>
<item>Ed McMahon stands here, lost in thought. Seeing you, he bellows, &quot;YES SIR!&quot;</item>
<item>...thingy???</item>
<item>It&apos;s 1000 secrets the government doesn&apos;t want you to know!</item>
<item>The letters O and R.</item>
<item>A magical... magic thing.</item>
</root>
